so let's see if we can compare the
flashdisk and the combination of the two
let's say that we have a user who will
play a game for two hours and the game
issues reads to two gigabytes of data
and rights to another ten megabytes of
data and then after these two hours the
user switches to watching a movie for
two hours where throughout these two
hours we will read one gigabyte
sequentially and then the user does this
three more times if we have a disk that
can read 100 megabytes a second if we
read sequentially and read or write one
megabyte per second if we do it randomly
and if you have flash that can access
one gigabyte per second either way what
is the total access time for all of the
data here if we use disk what is the
total access time with the disk in this
hole four times four hours what is the
total access time if we use pure flash
and what is the total access time if we
have a disk and a 4 gigabyte flash cache
that is initially empty